I think that would be a separate topic that you can talk to our competitor about,
but that's not something that we see. I would also say that it is not a straightforward thing
to replace established therapies like aromatase inhibitors that have been used for decades.
So I think this is something that will take time. I think when you look at the data in almost any
class of drug, when you're trying to replace a very established therapy, it requires a lot
of education and a lot of work, and that ramp will come up over time. So, you know, we don't,
we don't do this as having an impact on the Kiskali outlook, particularly now that in the
first-line setting, it seems clear that CDK4-6 will remain the standard of care for the remainder
of Kiskali's life cycle. Our focus very much is on CDK2, CDK2-4, CDK4 to make sure that we can
life cycle. Kiskali, you saw us bring in PIKivation, which we think has the opportunity
to be a pan-mutant PIK3CA that has the,
ability to avoid some of the toxicity profiles that we've seen with hyperglycemia and off-target
toxicities. So that could be an exciting medicine that hopefully might be able to
be used broadly in the approximately 50% of patients who have those mutations over time,
and then developing the combination drug studies, which we continue to do with the
oral cert companies. Thank you. Thank you. Your next question comes from the line of
Michael Leusten.
Welcome, Jefferies. Please go ahead.
Thank you. Last question for you on avidity. So, Dyn Therapeutics presented the achieved
data recently with a splicing correction at months three to 11 at a higher rate than we've
seen with daldesirin, and they also showed positive trends in MDHI, where I think we
haven't seen any data for daldesirin. Can you elaborate on how this data fits with your
decision to pursue avidity as opposed to other assets?
Yeah, absolutely. You know, I think
obviously the way biomarker data, splicing correction data, ultimately correlates with
function is to be determined. And I think this is obviously a complex topic, given that
the target here is in the nucleus. And so it's definitely something where you're going
to have different profiles for the different drugs, given that we're comparing here an
siRNA versus an ASO versus other technologies that are being deployed. You know, when we